Willowbrook Review Panel; Records apap127
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Community Placement [RESTRICTED], 1974-1981; 5; 19.8 cubic ft.
  - Community Placement Administrative Files [RESTRICTED], 1974-1981; 5.4; 7 cubic ft.
    - "Planning for Placements", Report, Appendices [RESTRICTED], 1978 (Box 5 (5-Community Placement [RESTRICTED]), Folder 18)
    - Professional Advisory Board, Medical Exemption From Programming Requests [RESTRICTED], 1979-1980 (Box 5 (5-Community Placement [RESTRICTED]), Folder 19)
    - Professional Advisory Board, Medical Exemption From Programming Requests [RESTRICTED], 1979-1980 (Box 5 (5-Community Placement [RESTRICTED]), Folder 20)
    - Professional Advisory Board, Medical Exemptions from Programming Requests [RESTRICTED], 1979-1980 (Box 6 (5-Community Placement [RESTRICTED]), Folder 1)
    - Purchase of Service Contract [RESTRICTED], 1974-1977 (Box 6 (5-Community Placement [RESTRICTED]), Folder 2)
    - Questioned Placements [RESTRICTED], 1978 (Box 6 (5-Community Placement [RESTRICTED]), Folder 3)
    - Regulations and Standards, Part 86 and 87 [RESTRICTED], 1978 (Box 6 (5-Community Placement [RESTRICTED]), Folder 4)
    - "Relationship of County Service Group to the B500, By Function", Report [RESTRICTED], 1979 (Box 6 (5-Community Placement [RESTRICTED]), Folder 5)
    - Speaker Bureaus, Community Representative Meeting Materials [RESTRICTED], 1977-1980 (Box 6 (5-Community Placement [RESTRICTED]), Folder 6)
    - Staten Island Community Services, Family Care Survey [RESTRICTED], 1977 (Box 6 (5-Community Placement [RESTRICTED]), Folder 7)
    - Staten Island Community Services, Family Care Survey [RESTRICTED], 1977 (Box 6 (5-Community Placement [RESTRICTED]), Folder 8)
    - Staten Island Community Services, Family Care Survey [RESTRICTED], 1977 (Box 6 (5-Community Placement [RESTRICTED]), Folder 9)
    - Staten Island Community Services, Family Care Survey [RESTRICTED], 1977 (Box 6 (5-Community Placement [RESTRICTED]), Folder 10)
    - Staten Island Community Services, Family Care Survey [RESTRICTED], 1977 (Box 6 (5-Community Placement [RESTRICTED]), Folder 11)
    - Staten Island Community Services, Family Care Survey [RESTRICTED], 1977 (Box 6 (5-Community Placement [RESTRICTED]), Folder 12)
    - Staten Island Community Services, Family Care Survey [RESTRICTED], 1977 (Box 6 (5-Community Placement [RESTRICTED]), Folder 13)
    - Staten Island Community Services, Family Care Survey [RESTRICTED], 1977 (Box 6 (5-Community Placement [RESTRICTED]), Folder 14)
    - Staten Island Community Services, Family Care Survey [RESTRICTED], 1977 (Box 6 (5-Community Placement [RESTRICTED]), Folder 15)
    - Transfers [RESTRICTED], 1980 February (Box 6 (5-Community Placement [RESTRICTED]), Folder 16)
    - Transfers [RESTRICTED], 1980 March (Box 6 (5-Community Placement [RESTRICTED]), Folder 17)
    - Transfers [RESTRICTED], 1980 April (Box 6 (5-Community Placement [RESTRICTED]), Folder 18)
    - Upstate Placement Unit [RESTRICTED], 1977 (Box 6 (5-Community Placement [RESTRICTED]), Folder 19)
    - Upstate Placement Unit [RESTRICTED], 1977; 1979 (Box 6 (5-Community Placement [RESTRICTED]), Folder 20)
    - Upstate Placement Unit [RESTRICTED], 1979 (Box 6 (5-Community Placement [RESTRICTED]), Folder 21)
    - Upstate Placement Unit, Operational Plan [RESTRICTED], 1977 (Box 6 (5-Community Placement [RESTRICTED]), Folder 22)
    - Upstate Willowbrook Class by 0050 Location [RESTRICTED], 1978 (Box 6 (5-Community Placement [RESTRICTED]), Folder 23)
    - Upstate Willowbrook Class Placements [RESTRICTED], 1978-1980 (Box 6 (5-Community Placement [RESTRICTED]), Folder 24)
    - Upstate Willowbrook Class Placements [RESTRICTED], 1978-1980 (Box 6 (5-Community Placement [RESTRICTED]), Folder 25)
    - Waivers of 30 Day Notice Requirement [RESTRICTED], 1978 (Box 7 (5-Community Placement [RESTRICTED]), Folder 1)
    - Willowbrook Class of 1972, Alphabetical List [RESTRICTED], 1979 December (Box 7 (5-Community Placement [RESTRICTED]), Folder 2)
    - Willowbrook Class of 1972, Alphabetical List [RESTRICTED], 1979 January (Box 7 (5-Community Placement [RESTRICTED]), Folder 3)
    - Willowbrook Class of 1972, Alphabetical List [RESTRICTED], 1979 February (Box 7 (5-Community Placement [RESTRICTED]), Folder 4)
    - Willowbrook Class of 1972, Alphabetical List [RESTRICTED], 1979 March (Box 7 (5-Community Placement [RESTRICTED]), Folder 5)
    - Willowbrook Class of 1972, Alphabetical List [RESTRICTED], 1979 April (Box 7 (5-Community Placement [RESTRICTED]), Folder 6)
    - Willowbrook Class of 1972, Alphabetical List [RESTRICTED], 1979 November (Box 7 (5-Community Placement [RESTRICTED]), Folder 7)
    - Willowbrook Class of 1972, Alphabetical List [RESTRICTED], 1979 March (Box 7 (5-Community Placement [RESTRICTED]), Folder 8)
    - Willowbrook Class of 1972, Alphabetical List [RESTRICTED], 1979 April (Box 7 (5-Community Placement [RESTRICTED]), Folder 9)
    - Willowbrook Class of 1972, Alphabetical List [RESTRICTED], 1979 June (Box 7 (5-Community Placement [RESTRICTED]), Folder 10)
    - Willowbrook Class of 1972, Alphabetical Listing [RESTRICTED], 1981 July (Box 7 (5-Community Placement [RESTRICTED]), Folder 11)
    - Willowbrook Class of 1972, Alphabetical Listing [RESTRICTED], 1981 August (Box 7 (5-Community Placement [RESTRICTED]), Folder 12)
    - Willowbrook Class of 1972, Facility Listing [RESTRICTED], 1979 December (Box 7 (5-Community Placement [RESTRICTED]), Folder 13)
    - Willowbrook Class of 1972, Facility Listing [RESTRICTED], 1980 January (Box 7 (5-Community Placement [RESTRICTED]), Folder 14)
    - Willowbrook Class of 1972, Facility Listing [RESTRICTED], 1980 February (Box 7 (5-Community Placement [RESTRICTED]), Folder 15)
    - Willowbrook Class of 1972, Facility Listing [RESTRICTED], 1980 March (Box 7 (5-Community Placement [RESTRICTED]), Folder 16)
    - Willowbrook Class of 1972, Facility Listing [RESTRICTED], 1980 April (Box 7 (5-Community Placement [RESTRICTED]), Folder 17)
    - Willowbrook Class of 1972, Facility Listing [RESTRICTED], 1980 November (Box 7 (5-Community Placement [RESTRICTED]), Folder 18)
    - Willowbrook Class of 1972, Facility Listing [RESTRICTED], 1981 March (Box 7 (5-Community Placement [RESTRICTED]), Folder 19)
    - Willowbrook Class of 1972, Facility Listing [RESTRICTED], 1981 April (Box 7 (5-Community Placement [RESTRICTED]), Folder 20)
    - Willowbrook Class of 1972, Facility Listing [RESTRICTED], 1981 June (Box 7 (5-Community Placement [RESTRICTED]), Folder 21)
    - Willowbrook Class of 1972, Facility Listing [RESTRICTED], 1981 July (Box 7 (5-Community Placement [RESTRICTED]), Folder 22)
    - Willowbrook Class of 1972, Facility Listing [RESTRICTED], 1981 August (Box 7 (5-Community Placement [RESTRICTED]), Folder 23)
    - Willowbrook Non-Class of 1972, Alphabetical List [RESTRICTED], 1981 June (Box 7 (5-Community Placement [RESTRICTED]), Folder 24)
    - Willowbrook Non-Class of 1972, Facility List [RESTRICTED], 1981 June (Box 7 (5-Community Placement [RESTRICTED]), Folder 25)
- New York State Department of Mental Hygiene/Office of Mental Retardation and Developmental Disabilities (NYS DMH/OMRDD) [RESTRICTED], 1975-1981; 6; 7.6 cubic ft.
  The series consists of correspondence, reports, and other materials relating to the implementation of the Willowbrook Consent Decree by the New York State Department of Mental Hygiene (known as the 'Office of Mental Retardation and Developmental Disabilities' from 1978 to the present). The papers are arranged alphabetically, some by topic (e.g., Community Residential Facilities, Hepatitis B Carriers), others by office of origin (e.g., Office of Counsel); in most cases these reflect the original record-keeping system. The two largest groups of materials in the series are: Commissioner's Correspondence which includes correspondence to and from the four men who held the office of DMH/OMRDD commissioner from 1975 to 1981; and Technical Assistance Unit/Consent Decree Office which includes materials by and about the specific office of the DMH/OMRDD charged with implementing the Consent Decree. The series is restricted because it contains information about specific named residents of Willowbrook and other state developmental centers. Most of the material in this series is in letter-sized format. The last box contains legal-sized material in a separate alphabetical arrangement.
  - Administration, Division of [RESTRICTED], 1976-1977 (Box 1 (6-New York State Department of Mental ), Folder 1)
  - Alternative Methods of Care For the Aged and Chronically Ill, Report of Task Force On [RESTRICTED], 1976 (Box 1 (6-New York State Department of Mental ), Folder 2)
  - Annual Plan for Mental Retardation Services [RESTRICTED], 1976 (Box 1 (6-New York State Department of Mental ), Folder 3)
  - "Background for a Community Placement Plan" [RESTRICTED], 1975 (Box 1 (6-New York State Department of Mental ), Folder 4)
  - Borough Developmental Services Office, Queens, Implementation Plan [RESTRICTED], 1979 (Box 1 (6-New York State Department of Mental ), Folder 5)
  - Borough Developmental Services Offices, Self-Survey [RESTRICTED], 1978 (Box 1 (6-New York State Department of Mental ), Folder 6)
  - Budget [RESTRICTED], 1976-1977 (Box 1 (6-New York State Department of Mental ), Folder 7)
  - Budget and Fiscal Services/ Fiscal Management [RESTRICTED], 1975-1976 (Box 1 (6-New York State Department of Mental ), Folder 8)
  - Budget, Executive [RESTRICTED], 1976-1979 (Box 1 (6-New York State Department of Mental ), Folder 9)
  - Business Office [RESTRICTED], 1977-1979 (Box 1 (6-New York State Department of Mental ), Folder 10)
  - Capital Budget Requests, Fiscal Year 1979-1980 [RESTRICTED] (Box 1 (6-New York State Department of Mental ), Folder 11)
  - Central Office Memos [RESTRICTED], 1975-1980 (Box 1 (6-New York State Department of Mental ), Folder 12)
  - Client Information Services, Bureau of Patient Resources [RESTRICTED], 1975-1977 (Box 1 (6-New York State Department of Mental ), Folder 13)
  - Clinical Control Unit Special Review Committee [RESTRICTED], 1977 (Box 1 (6-New York State Department of Mental ), Folder 14)
  - Commissioner's Correspondence, Lawrence C. Kolb [RESTRICTED], 1975-1977 (Box 1 (6-New York State Department of Mental ), Folder 15)
  - Commissioner's Correspondence, Lawrence C. Kolb [RESTRICTED], 1975-1977 (Box 1 (6-New York State Department of Mental ), Folder 16)
  - Commissioner's Correspondence, James A. Prevast [RESTRICTED], 1978 (Box 1 (6-New York State Department of Mental ), Folder 17)
  - Commissioner's Correspondence, Thomas A. Coughlin III [RESTRICTED], 1975 October-1976 March (Box 1 (6-New York State Department of Mental ), Folder 18)
  - Commissioner's Correspondence, Thomas A. Coughlin III [RESTRICTED], 1976 April-1976 November (Box 1 (6-New York State Department of Mental ), Folder 19)
  - Commissioner's Correspondence, Thomas A. Coughlin III [RESTRICTED], 1976 December-1977 March (Box 1 (6-New York State Department of Mental ), Folder 20)
  - Commissioner's Correspondence, Thomas A. Coughlin III [RESTRICTED], 1977 March-1977 June (Box 1 (6-New York State Department of Mental ), Folder 21)
  - Commissioner's Correspondence, Thomas A. Coughlin III [RESTRICTED], 1977 July-1977 August (Box 1 (6-New York State Department of Mental ), Folder 22)
  - Commissioner's Correspondence, Thomas A. Coughlin III [RESTRICTED], 1977 September-1977 October (Box 1 (6-New York State Department of Mental ), Folder 23)
  - Commissioner's Correspondence, Thomas A. Coughlin III [RESTRICTED], 1977 November-1977 December (Box 1 (6-New York State Department of Mental ), Folder 24)
  - Commissioner's Correspondence, Thomas A. Coughlin III [RESTRICTED], 1978 January-1978 February (Box 1 (6-New York State Department of Mental ), Folder 25)
  - Commissioner's Correspondence, Thomas A. Coughlin III [RESTRICTED], 1978 March-1978 April (Box 1 (6-New York State Department of Mental ), Folder 26)
  - Commissioner's Correspondence, Thomas A. Coughlin III [RESTRICTED], 1978 May-1978 June (Box 1 (6-New York State Department of Mental ), Folder 27)
  - Commissioner's Correspondence, Thomas A. Coughlin III [RESTRICTED], 1978 July-1978 October (Box 1 (6-New York State Department of Mental ), Folder 28)
  - Commissioner's Correspondence, Thomas A. Coughlin III [RESTRICTED], 1978 November-1978 December (Box 2 (6-New York State Department of Mental ), Folder 1)
  - Commissioner's Correspondence, Thomas A. Coughlin III [RESTRICTED], 1979-1980 (Box 2 (6-New York State Department of Mental ), Folder 2)
  - Community Placement Costs [RESTRICTED], 1977 (Box 2 (6-New York State Department of Mental ), Folder 3)
  - Community Residences Report [RESTRICTED], 1978 (Box 2 (6-New York State Department of Mental ), Folder 4)
  - Commissioner's Correspondence (James E. Introne) [RESTRICTED], 1979-1981 (Box 2 (6-New York State Department of Mental ), Folder 5)
  - Commissioner's Correspondence (James E. Introne) [RESTRICTED], 1979-1981 (Box 2 (6-New York State Department of Mental ), Folder 6)
  - Commissioner's Correspondence (James E. Introne) [RESTRICTED], 1979-1981 (Box 2 (6-New York State Department of Mental ), Folder 7)
  - Community Care and Family Residence Checklists [RESTRICTED], 1977-1978; Undated (Box 2 (6-New York State Department of Mental ), Folder 8)
  - Community Care and Family Residence Standards [RESTRICTED], 1973; 1977; Undated (Box 2 (6-New York State Department of Mental ), Folder 9)
  - Community Residence Alternatives Plan, Section 1 [RESTRICTED], 1979 (Box 2 (6-New York State Department of Mental ), Folder 10)
  - Community Residence Alternatives Plan, Section 1 [RESTRICTED], 1979 (Box 2 (6-New York State Department of Mental ), Folder 11)
  - Community Residence Alternatives Plan, Section 2 [RESTRICTED], 1979 (Box 2 (6-New York State Department of Mental ), Folder 12)
  - Community Residence Alternatives Plan, Section 3 [RESTRICTED], 1979 (Box 2 (6-New York State Department of Mental ), Folder 13)
  - Community Residence Alternatives Plan, Section 3 [RESTRICTED], 1979 (Box 2 (6-New York State Department of Mental ), Folder 14)
  - Community Residence Alternatives Plan, Section 3 [RESTRICTED], 1979 (Box 2 (6-New York State Department of Mental ), Folder 15)
  - Community Residential Facilities [RESTRICTED], Undated (Box 2 (6-New York State Department of Mental ), Folder 16)
  - Consent Judgement Compliance [RESTRICTED], 1976 (Box 2 (6-New York State Department of Mental ), Folder 17)
  - Consent Judgment Policy Interpretations [RESTRICTED], 1978-1980 (Box 2 (6-New York State Department of Mental ), Folder 18)
  - Correspondence, General [RESTRICTED], 1976-1980 (Box 2 (6-New York State Department of Mental ), Folder 19)
  - Coughlin, Thomas A. III- Desposition in Society for Good Will to Retarded Children Inc. v. Carey [RESTRICTED], 1980 (Box 2 (6-New York State Department of Mental ), Folder 20)
  - Counsel, Office of [RESTRICTED], 1975-1980 (Box 3 (6-New York State Department of Mental ), Folder 1)
  - Counsel, Office of [RESTRICTED], 1975-1980 (Box 3 (6-New York State Department of Mental ), Folder 2)
  - Counsel, Office of [RESTRICTED], 1975-1980 (Box 3 (6-New York State Department of Mental ), Folder 3)
  - Developmental Disabilities Service Office, Organizational Charts and Assessments [RESTRICTED], Undated (Box 3 (6-New York State Department of Mental ), Folder 4)
  - Directory of Children and Adult Mental Hygiene Facilities in New York City [RESTRICTED], 1977 (Box 3 (6-New York State Department of Mental ), Folder 5)
  - Due Process, D-4 [RESTRICTED], 1976-1979 (Box 3 (6-New York State Department of Mental ), Folder 6)
  - Due Process, Memoranda no. 76-5 and 77-2, Addendum [RESTRICTED], 1977-1979 (Box 3 (6-New York State Department of Mental ), Folder 7)
  - Due Process, Memoranda no. 75-10 [RESTRICTED], 1975-1976 (Box 3 (6-New York State Department of Mental ), Folder 8)
  - Due Process, Memoranda no. 75-10 [RESTRICTED], 1975-1976 (Box 3 (6-New York State Department of Mental ), Folder 9)
  - Due Process, Memoranda no. 76-5 [RESTRICTED], 1976 (Box 3 (6-New York State Department of Mental ), Folder 10)
  - Due Process, Memoranda no. 76-5 [RESTRICTED], 1979-1980 (Box 3 (6-New York State Department of Mental ), Folder 11)
  - Due Process Procedures [RESTRICTED], 1976-1980 (Box 3 (6-New York State Department of Mental ), Folder 12)
  - Due Process, Transfers to Psychiatric Centers [RESTRICTED], 1977 (Box 3 (6-New York State Department of Mental ), Folder 13)
  - Due Process, W-3 [RESTRICTED], 1975-1977 (Box 3 (6-New York State Department of Mental ), Folder 14)
  - DVP User's Manual [RESTRICTED], 1979 (Box 3 (6-New York State Department of Mental ), Folder 15)
  - Education, Bureau of [RESTRICTED], 1977 (Box 3 (6-New York State Department of Mental ), Folder 16)
  - Evaluation and Inspection, Office of [RESTRICTED], 1977-1978 (Box 3 (6-New York State Department of Mental ), Folder 17)
  - Facilities Developmental Corporation [RESTRICTED], Undated (Box 3 (6-New York State Department of Mental ), Folder 18)
  - Facilities Developmental Corporation [RESTRICTED], Undated (Box 3 (6-New York State Department of Mental ), Folder 19)
  - Family Care [RESTRICTED], 1976-1977 (Box 3 (6-New York State Department of Mental ), Folder 20)
  - Family Care Homes, Standards for [RESTRICTED], 1977-1978 (Box 3 (6-New York State Department of Mental ), Folder 21)
  - Family Care/ Medicaid [RESTRICTED], 1977-1979 (Box 3 (6-New York State Department of Mental ), Folder 22)
  - First Deputy Commissioner [RESTRICTED], 1975-1980 (Box 3 (6-New York State Department of Mental ), Folder 23)
  - "Final Report of the Task Force for the Development of Community..." [RESTRICTED], 1975 (Box 3 (6-New York State Department of Mental ), Folder 24)
  - "Final Report of the Task Force for the Development of Community..." [RESTRICTED], 1975 (Box 3 (6-New York State Department of Mental ), Folder 25)
  - Health Services [RESTRICTED], 1975-1978; 1980 (Box 3 (6-New York State Department of Mental ), Folder 26)
  - Health Services [RESTRICTED], 1975-1978; 1980 (Box 3 (6-New York State Department of Mental ), Folder 27)
  - Hepatitis B Carriers (1-2 of 8) [RESTRICTED], 1975-1981 (Box 3 (6-New York State Department of Mental ), Folder 28-29)
  - Hepatitis B Carriers (3-8 of 8) [RESTRICTED], 1975-1981 (Box 4 (6-New York State Department of Mental ), Folder 1-6)
  - Individual Development Plan [RESTRICTED], 1975-1980 (Box 4 (6-New York State Department of Mental ), Folder 7)
  - Individual Development Plan [RESTRICTED], 1975-1980 (Box 4 (6-New York State Department of Mental ), Folder 8)
  - Individual Program Plan Forms [RESTRICTED], 1980 (Box 4 (6-New York State Department of Mental ), Folder 9)
  - Information Systems and Management Analysis; Management and Office Systems [RESTRICTED], 1976-1977 (Box 4 (6-New York State Department of Mental ), Folder 10)
  - Institution Services (Engineering Services) [RESTRICTED], 1976 (Box 4 (6-New York State Department of Mental ), Folder 11)
  - Institutional Returns/ Readmissions [RESTRICTED], 1980 (Box 4 (6-New York State Department of Mental ), Folder 12)
  - Intergroup Relations, Office Form [RESTRICTED], 1975-1977 (Box 4 (6-New York State Department of Mental ), Folder 13)
  - Intermediate Care Facilities for the Mentally Retarded [RESTRICTED], ca. 1975-1977 (Box 4 (6-New York State Department of Mental ), Folder 14)
  - Job Statements [RESTRICTED], 1979 (Box 4 (6-New York State Department of Mental ), Folder 15)
  - Leasing and Purchase Plans [RESTRICTED], ca. 1977 (Box 4 (6-New York State Department of Mental ), Folder 16)
  - Long Island County Services Group [RESTRICTED], 1978-1979 (Box 4 (6-New York State Department of Mental ), Folder 17)
  - Manpower/Employee Relations Personnel [RESTRICTED], 1975-1979 (Box 4 (6-New York State Department of Mental ), Folder 18)
  - Manpower/Employee Relations Personnel [RESTRICTED], 1975-1979 (Box 4 (6-New York State Department of Mental ), Folder 19)
  - Memorandum of Understanding Between the Willowbrook Review Panel and the Defendants in the Willowbrook Case [RESTRICTED], 1976 (Box 4 (6-New York State Department of Mental ), Folder 20)
  - Mental Health, Divisions of (Mental Retardation and Children's Services) [RESTRICTED], 1975-1980 (Box 4 (6-New York State Department of Mental ), Folder 21)
  - Mental Hygiene Law [RESTRICTED], 1975-1978 (Box 4 (6-New York State Department of Mental ), Folder 22)
  - Mental Hygiene Law- Amendment [RESTRICTED], Undated (Box 4 (6-New York State Department of Mental ), Folder 23)
  - Mental Retardation, Division of [RESTRICTED], 1975-1977 (Box 4 (6-New York State Department of Mental ), Folder 24)
  - Monthly Expenditure Report [RESTRICTED], 1977-1978 (Box 4 (6-New York State Department of Mental ), Folder 25)
  - Monthly Statistics [RESTRICTED], 1976 (Box 4 (6-New York State Department of Mental ), Folder 26)
  - New Agency Forms [RESTRICTED], 1978 (Box 4 (6-New York State Department of Mental ), Folder 27)
  - New York State Advisory Council on Development Disabilities on Willowbrook State School, Report of the [RESTRICTED], Undated (Box 4 (6-New York State Department of Mental ), Folder 28)
  - Non-Residential Class Members [RESTRICTED], 1977-1978 (Box 4 (6-New York State Department of Mental ), Folder 29)
  - Nutrition Services/ Supply Support [RESTRICTED], 1975-1977 (Box 4 (6-New York State Department of Mental ), Folder 30)
  - Operational Plans [RESTRICTED], 1977 (Box 4 (6-New York State Department of Mental ), Folder 31)
  - Operational Plan Correspondence [RESTRICTED], 1978 (Box 4 (6-New York State Department of Mental ), Folder 32)
  - Operational Plan Objectives [RESTRICTED], 1975-1976 (Box 4 (6-New York State Department of Mental ), Folder 33)
  - Operational Plan Objectives [RESTRICTED], 1976-1977 (Box 5 (6-New York State Department of Mental ), Folder 1)
  - Operational Plan Objectives [RESTRICTED], 1976-1977 (Box 5 (6-New York State Department of Mental ), Folder 2)
  - NYS DMH/ OMRDD [RESTRICTED], 1976-1977 (Box 5 (6-New York State Department of Mental ), Folder 3)
  - Personnel, Grievance [RESTRICTED], 1976 (Box 5 (6-New York State Department of Mental ), Folder 4)
  - Placements, Operational Plan for [RESTRICTED], 1980 (Box 5 (6-New York State Department of Mental ), Folder 5)
  - Placements, Operational Plan for [RESTRICTED], 1980 (Box 5 (6-New York State Department of Mental ), Folder 6)
  - Policy and Procedures Manuel [RESTRICTED], 1976-1980 (Box 5 (6-New York State Department of Mental ), Folder 7)
  - Policy and Procedures Manuel [RESTRICTED], 1976-1980 (Box 5 (6-New York State Department of Mental ), Folder 8)
  - Policy and Procedures Manuel [RESTRICTED], 1976-1980 (Box 5 (6-New York State Department of Mental ), Folder 9)
  - Procedures [RESTRICTED], 1978 (Box 5 (6-New York State Department of Mental ), Folder 10)
  - Press Releases [RESTRICTED], 1979 (Box 5 (6-New York State Department of Mental ), Folder 11)
  - Program Resources Manual [RESTRICTED], 1978 (Box 5 (6-New York State Department of Mental ), Folder 12)
  - Program Resources Manual [RESTRICTED], 1978 (Box 5 (6-New York State Department of Mental ), Folder 13)
  - Project Management Group (Samuel J. Kawola) [RESTRICTED], 1980 (Box 5 (6-New York State Department of Mental ), Folder 14)
  - Psychotherapeutic Drugs, Manual on [RESTRICTED], 1977-1979 (Box 5 (6-New York State Department of Mental ), Folder 15)
  - Public Relations, Volunteer Services [RESTRICTED], 1976 (Box 5 (6-New York State Department of Mental ), Folder 16)
  - Regional Offices- Nassau-Suffolk [RESTRICTED], 1978 (Box 5 (6-New York State Department of Mental ), Folder 17)
  - Regional Offices- New York City [RESTRICTED], 1976-1978 (Box 5 (6-New York State Department of Mental ), Folder 18)
  - Regional Offices and Facilities [RESTRICTED], 1976 (Box 5 (6-New York State Department of Mental ), Folder 19)